

HR OFFICER

Details

13th July 36/1 Bitola, 7000

Macedonia

+38978256951

jbiberovikj@yahoo.com

NATIONALITY

Macedonian

DATE / PLACE OF BIRTH

27.10.1993

Bitola

Links

LinkedIn

Skills

Adaptability

Employee Relations

Critical thinking and problem solving

Analytical and Problem-Solving skills

Teamwork

Leadership

Empathy

Communication Skills

Creativity

Ability to Multitask

Effective Time Management

Ability to Work Under Pressure

Decision Making

Microsoft Office

Profile

An enthusiastic person and former Professional Basketball Player with the current filed of work that specializes in operative excellence and previous experience of an HR/ Employee Relations Officer. As HR Officer I improved my motivational and problem-solving skills that were driven from the development of emotional intelligence. My goal is to sharpen my skills, gain more knowledge in any possible field, and to turn challenges into meaningful changes.

- 4 x National Basketball Champion in the republic of North Macedonia;
- Achieved 5 medals at AAU Tournaments in the United States of America;
- Member of the professional basketball club Feni Industry.

Employment History

HR Officer, Kromberg & Schubert, Bitola

SEPTEMBER 2020 - NOVEMBER 2021

- Interviewed over 1000 employees;
- Created daily absence reports;
- Conducted over 50 Surveys;
- · Created monthly fluctuation reports;
- Transferred over 1500 employees;
- Signed over 3000 contracts;
- Created over 900 cards and transportation tokens for the new employees;
- Created multiple projects that reduced the number of absences, sick leaves, and fluctuation:
- Created ideas that motivated the employees to get vaccinated;
- Provided to the Payroll Team (Payroll deductions, working hours, regulated health booklets;
- Provided help to the Administration Team (Created over 400 Contracts)
- Entered over 200 employees in the Payroll System.

HR Employee Relations Officer, Kromberg & Schubert, Bitola

SEPTEMBER 2020 - NOVEMBER 2021

- Issued over 800 Warning and Coaching Letters and Letters for Improvement;
- Gave over 200 feed backs to employees that had Letters for Improvement;
- Signed over 4000 contracts;
- · Conducted over 100 Surveys;
- Coached over 20 Team Leaders, Shift Leaders and Coordinators to improve their performances.

HR/Production Trainer, Kromberg & Schubert Bitola, Bitola

JULY 2018 - JANUARY 2019

- Trained and monitored over 700 employees;
- Coached over 50 Team Leaders to get better and improve their performance.

Child Development assistant , Danville Area Community College, Danville, IL

NOVEMBER 2014 - MAY 2015

• Helped Child Development Teachers

Education

Criminal Justice and Psychology, Central Methodist University, Fayette

SEPTEMBER 2015 - MAY 2015

Adobe Photoshop

First Aid & CPR

Hobbies

Basketball, Hiking, Photography, Mountain Biking, PlayStation, Designing

Languages

Macedonian

English

Completed my Junior year at Central Methodist University, Transferred to Brock University in St. Catherine's ON, Canada, Enrolled and got accepted to complete program in Criminal Justice and Psychology but my application for student visa got denied and I had to return to Macedonia.

Criminal Justice and Sport and Management , Danville Area Community College, Danville

SEPTEMBER 2014 - MAY 2015

Graduated with an AA Degree in Social Sciences,

Criminal Justice, Iowa Central Community College, Fort Dodge

SEPTEMBER 2013 - MAY 2014

Marquette Catholic High School, Michigan City

SEPTEMBER 2011 - JUNE 2013

Graduated from Marquette Catholic High School

Metodi Mitevski Birco, Skopje

SEPTEMBER 2010 - JUNE 2011

Completed Second year of High School

Gjorgji Naumov, Bitola

SEPTEMBER 2009 - JUNE 2010

Completed first year of High School

Primary Education, Elpida Karamandi, Bitola

SEPTEMBER 2001 - JUNE 2009

References

Community Service Programs

Community Service , Michigan City

JANUARY 2011 - FEBRUARY 2013

Helping the people from Michigan City,

Buying need and goods to the elder people, cleaning the environment, painting homes and schools, basketball summer camps. All together 100 hours of Community Service.

Community Service, Fayette

SEPTEMBER 2015 - APRIL 2016

Helping the people from Fayette MO, that were living near the University Campus.

Buying need and goods to the elderly citizens, cleaning the environment, attended social programs for abused children. All together 120 hours of Community Service.

Special Olympiad games, Fort Dodge

NOVEMBER 2013 - DECEMBER 2013

Training and preparing kids with special needs to attend Special Olympiad games.